Guide to the Rachel Marshall Goetz Papers 1898-1994
University of Chicago Library
- Series V: Audio Material
  Series V contains reel-to-reel and cassette tapes with a variety of content. Most of the reel-to-reel tapes are unidentified. The cassette tapes include a series of oral history interviews conducted with Goetz by Mary Alzina Stone Dale, daughter of Goetz’s close friend, Ursula Batchelder Stone.
  Series V: Audio Material
  - Six 7" audio tape reels, unidentified, n.d. (Box 16)
  - Six 7" audio tape reels, unidentified, 1956 and n.d. (Box 17)
  - Six 7" audio tape reels, unidentified, n.d. (Box 18)
  - Two 5" audio tape reels, unidentified, n.d. (Box 19)
  - Four 7" audio tape reels, unidentified, n.d. (Box 19)
  - Fifteen 3" audio tape reels, unidentified, 1961-1963 and n.d. (Box 20)
  - Sixteen audio cassette tapes, oral histories, 1987-1992 (Box 21)
- Series VI: Oversize Material and Artifacts
  Series VI contains oversize material and artifacts transferred from previous series. Included here are Goetz’s collection of campaign pins from Adlai Stevenson’s 1956 presidential campaign and a box of slides containing supporting material for her early-1950s work, "Visual Aids and State Governments." Also housed in this series are two large photographs of Goetz from 1930, an oversized map of the Hyde Park-Kenwood Urban Renewal Project dated 1960, and a poster voicing the Hyde Park League of Women Voters’ support for the 1945 United Nations World Security Conference.
  - 10 Adlai Stevenson campaign pins, 1956 (Box 22)
  - Slides from "Visual Aids and State Governments," n.d. (Box 22)
  - Rachel Goetz, black and white studio portrait, c. 1930 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Hyde Park-Kenwood Urban Renewal Project, Community Conservation Board of Chicago, Neighborhood Redevelopment Map, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - United Nations World Security Conference Poster, Hyde Park League of Women Voters, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Visual Aids and State Governments, Asian-language poster, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 4)